Injury wise, I don't think y'all had
anything major come out of yesterday.
>> No, nothing major came out of yesterday.
>> You did say that Burrow will play.
Is there was there any consideration to
not have him play in that game?
>> No. Gives us the best chance to win the
game.
>> Uh Joseph Osai, is he eligible to come
back?
>> We'll see. Yeah, he's eligible to come.
I mean, we didn't put him on or
anything. We'll see through the week and
and see where he ends up.
>> Has Chase Brown developed into a, for
lack of a better term, a complete
running back? I I have complete trust in
him in all three phases of playing
running [snorts] back, first and second
down runner, coming out of the back
field, being an empty um protection. Um
I think he's had some great clips of
protection this year as well. So um you
know I it's it's a loose term complete
back, but in terms of being able to be
really effective in all three phases, we
absolutely trust him to do that.
>> Joe goes perfect when he was not
pressured yesterday. 19 for 19. Just
looking back on the tape, I mean, what
do you see from him and just I mean,
continues to show how how great he is.
>> Yeah, I mean, that's nothing surprises
me with how he did it. I I think the
part of the game that he won't get
enough credit for is is their their
pressure package and their fronts and
different personnel groupings and
different alignments and how they attack
your protections on second down and
third down. this week was probably as as
difficult as as any week we have in
terms of identifying that. Um they'd
really hit home against a lot of teams.
And so I just think his his command
isn't something that people in the
stands are necessar
and and looking at how where a guy's
foot is and where his hand is. I mean,
all the things that he factored into it
um to make sure that we were we were on
point. I think that's that's an
underrated part of it. And I thought our
guys did a great job with the actual
picking it up, you know, understanding
what we're trying to do and doing a
great job with the protection aspect of
it.
>> Throwing the the Cody play out of it.
You were in six offensive linemen a
little bit more yesterday. Was there
something about that that was that game
plan or is that something you like?
>> No, that was again that's it's um their
personnel packages. You you weren't
going to see a lot of 11 on tape against
them. just just the way that they um you
know essentially give you base fronts
for the most part against that and so
you got to be in 12 and with Noah being
limited not knowing throughout the week
until the end that Noah was going to be
up you rep you know your second tight
end that they're going to they're going
to call a tight end out there blocking.
So um that was that was part of it and
then just okay well let's do something
fun to to energize the end of practice
and we did it and and then it just you
know kind of snowballed from there to
where he was out there. Amarius, I mean
it seems like he's had a really good
season. You know, you don't talk about
him and that's what shows that it's a
good season, I guess. What have you seen
from him maybe that people might not
notice that's been a growth from him
this year?
>> Well, I just think um not to dismiss his
football IQ going into this season, but
I think that's really grown what to
anticipate uh moves from from players,
how to come off in the run game. I just
think he's really starting to take that
next step of being able to anticipate
before it actually happens. And again,
I'm not trying to discount what he was
last year in college, but I just think
that experience is really starting to
pick up now to where he knows what's
coming at him and can be one step ahead
of all that. So, not only using his his
massive frame and all the great traits
that he has, now you get the the mental
edge on people because you know what
they're going to do before they do it.
Um, is a huge huge step for him. I know
that you're you'd rather some of these
questions answer after the the upcoming
games because they're more offseason
type questions, but is it at least
gratifying for you to have seen the way
that DJ and Dax have grown into their
spots and that you can go into the
offseason knowing like you have your
foundation at outside corner and then
specifically with Dax, he's played
safety, nickel,
>> I would assume that's really hard to be
able to master the outside corner the
way he has. So, can you just talk a
little bit about how they've grown into
their their positions and the players
and how you guys can build around them?
>> Yeah, we have a lot of confidence in
both those guys. Like you said, Dax has
Dax has done a lot for us over over his
four years here and I think his best
position is is outside of corner and and
he's done an excellent job of that. He's
got tremendous length and physicality
and speed and and again similar to what
we're talking about with other players
who are going through their second,
third, fourth year. Now the experience
is really showing up on how to
anticipate and so I just I think he's
really grown in the right direction
there and and somebody we can certainly
count on. And I've mentioned all that
about DJ several times over the course
of the season that hasn't changed for me
at all. I thought yesterday he was
outstanding with his energy and his
leadership and and his on ball defending
skills and I thought both those guys did
a great job yesterday.
>> So much focus Zach on the players and
rightfully so. But how has Al Golden
developed this year? How has the way he
manipulates like yesterday you know
holding Trey McBride in check for three
plus quarters. How has his schemes uh
grown? How have they grown and developed
over? Well, that that's why he's here,
you know, and I I just think I've got
such a high opinion of him and and he's
the proof is in the pudding with with
how he's coached when he was here, the
development he had at the linebacker
position, the effect he had, you know,
on on our Super Bowl team. Um, and then
going to Notre Dame and having the
success that he had, played for national
championship and developed a ton of
players along the way and now he's here
and and early in the season, you know,
we're we're playing a lot of guys that
are new to it and they're all developing
at the same time. And so now that he's
been able to these guys really
understand what we're asking of them
coaching staff by the way that's never
coached together before you know none of
those guys and with D. And so now for
everybody to get into a groove and now
you get to expand what we're asking
these guys to do and really attack teams
um you're really seeing what we're
capable of and and that's exciting. So
um I've seen that all all along. I've
known where this thing was headed. I've
known where this thing is going to end
up and we're going to continue to prove
in the offseason as well. put um I think
he's done a really good job, you know,
particularly since the buy. I mean,
since the by-week, you know, we gave up
31 to to however many to to Buffalo
outside the the pick six. Um the team
hasn't scored more than 19 against our
defense. You know, they've done a great
job creating turnovers, limiting drives,
and uh and giving us a great chance to
win.
>> The question a little bit, but why did
it take so long for defense to hit a
stride? By the way,
>> I think I said, you know, a lot of youth
on defense, a lot of guys getting their
first taste of playing. and we played
two rookie linebackers for a really long
time together. Um, some other young
players that have really done a great
job developing and that's credit to
them. That's credit to their coaches and
so now you see a really cohesive unit
that understands everything we're trying
to do. We understand their strengths and
playing in their strengths and um
they've got a lot of confidence and
that's a big part of things is just
establishing and maintaining that
confidence. It's it's a unit where all
11 guys are playing together. Um, which
is critical, you know, and about the
halfway point of the season, that's
that's where you started to really see
that and and so we just got to continue
to build off of that.
>> Just getting back to Marius real quick,
uh, how much of a factor Orlando has
been just the fact that he shows up and
as a veteran who kind of has his height
and frame and he's been through. Yeah, I
I think I I think Orlando's been a
tremendous leader from that standpoint
and helping Amarius grow. I think you
give credit to Orlando. I think you can
give credit to to Dalton as well playing
right guard next to him as well. I I
don't think um again I I give a lot of
credit to Marius and how much he's grown
with with the football queue of things
and and I think um Dalton's done a great
job as well, you know, talking through
after play what you see what you know
what how can I help you? Um, so again,
that's that's that's not um [sighs]
that's just a great combination of
people, you know, sitting there next to
each other communicating. And that's
that's what highlevel offensive lines do
is Ted communicating to the group from a
center standpoint. That's uh Dylan and
Ted. That's Dylan and Orlando. That's
Dalton and Ted. Dalton and Amarius. Um I
just think as a whole the communication
has been outstanding and Jaylen is more
than capable of as well when he's gotten
time in there. uh Lucas when he's been
in there, you know. So, it's just really
a really impressive group in terms of
the overall connection that they have
together and the chemistry and the
communication and I think that's why our
offensive line's playing the best since
I've been here, you know. It's that's
been fun to see.
>> Do you approach this week any
differently knowing that it is your last
game of the season? Maybe giving some
guys that contract is up or a younger
guy some more playing time to see what
they have.
>> No, whatever we can do to win the game
is what we're going to do. And on that
note, do you have any of those exit
interview type conversations? Do you use
the time this week with you being
eliminated or
>> No, our our focus 100% is on let's let's
keep this as normal as possible. Put in
a great week of work, finish strong with
a with a win in a divisional game at
home in front of our fans, finish on a
three-game winning streak. Um, those are
the focuses and then next week we do
next week.
>> You got a whole week to prep for Miles
Garrett. What's that week like compared
to maybe other guys around the league
that you'll see?
>> He's the best. I mean, he's he's he's
the best defensive player on planet
Earth. And so, um,
you know, it's it's he's he's
how you can't put into words. I mean,
he's hard to describe what your plan has
to be when you play against him. And
it's all hands on deck. Um, have as much
respect for him as as any player we've
ever gone against. Um, it's not a fun
process pregame. It's not a fun process
during the game. Um, we take a lot of
pride having a great plan to try to give
us our best chance of success. And I
think the fact that he's in position,
you know, where he's at for this record
is is uh a credit to him that he's done
it at such a high level repeatedly over
and over and over again. And and uh he's
an absolute nightmare. And so, no, I
don't enjoy one second of of preparing
for him. knowing that he's going to be
there's probably an extra bit on the
line for him this week to get that sack.
Does that affect how you guys
>> Every year we play him in week 18
there's something on the line for his
career. Last year it was his hundth
sack, you know, and so again, we're just
got to have a plan that puts us in the
best chance to win the game and and uh
he can handle whatever he's got to
handle, but but um if he plays I mean
the way he plays in week one and and I
mean he plays the same every week. So um
whether he's got something on the line
or not, he's he's got our full
attention. Looking back on that week one
game, he obviously has two sacks in that
one when you guys played them.
>> Where have you seen uh the biggest
difference both in the line and and this
team from from week one to now week 18
where where you are now coming off this
game yesterday
>> for us?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Well, I just think you know the the time
on task, you know, you got Dylan who's
now played
>> I think he's played also I can't
remember. Um you know he's he's played a
ton now at left guard. Um, Dalton
obviously has come in and and played a
good chunk of our season. And so I think
now you've just seen the continuity of
our offensive line and and once any any
team in the league, you know, gets the
first couple games under your belt. It
September is always a challenge to
reestablish your identity and figure out
what your strengths and weaknesses are
going to be and and you catch a better
groove, you know, in in November and
December on who you really are and what
your what you need to focus on and and
so I think just now we we know who we
are and um know our strengths and know
our weaknesses and and just got to keep
focusing on that stuff.
It's felt like the first victory Monday
in a bit. Is that right?
>> It's the only one
>> in in like last year. I don't remember
one.
>> I can't remember. Um I can't remember to
be honest with you.
>> Good.
>> Okay. Thank you. Thanks.